Software Engineer

### Hard Skills

Programming Languages: Java, C++, C#, Python, JavaScript, HTML, CSS, NodeJS, React, and MongoDB

Math: Calculus 1, 2, and 3 along with Linear Algebra

Other: Data structures, databases, version control, computer vision, automation with trajectory planning, interfacing with APIs, libraries, and motors/sensors, Android app development, PID control

## Soft Skills

- Working collaboratively in software development
- Teaching, lesson planning, written and oral communication
- Leadership, conflict resolution
- Critical thinking, problem-solving, and attention to detail

## Volunteer Work

I have spent hundreds of hours volunteering at FIRST Robotics competitions, spreading my passion for STEM to younger students. I also worked with my FRC Robotics team to attend outreach events at museums and fairs to share my love of STEM to even more people.

Student at the **University of Washington's Paul G. Allen School of Computer Science**. Multiple years of experience in **Robotics**, **Web Development**, and

#### Education

Henry M. Jackson High School

Sep 2019 – June 2023

High School Diploma, **Valedictorian** (GPA: 4.0) Member of FRC Team 2910

Everett Community College (Running Start)

Sep 2021 – June 2023

Associate in Art and Science, President's Distinction (GPA: 4.0)

University of Washington

Sep 2023 – Present

Paul G. Allen School of Computer Science

### **Awards**

- FRC Autonomous Award Sponsored by Ford (twice in 2022, once in 2023)
- 2023 Indiana Robotics Invitational Scholar, IRI Host Teams Scholarship
- AP Scholar, AP Scholar with Honor

# Experience

Computer Science Tutor – Coding With Kids Aug 2021 – April 2023

At this at Coding With Kids premier coding academy, I tutored young children in the basics of computer programming in languages like Scratch and Python.

Lead Software Developer – FRC Team 2910 Sept 2021 – July 2023

In High School, I was a member of a world-class robotics team. We finished 3<sup>rd</sup> place in the world in 2022 and won over 10 major competitions over these two years. On this team, I wrote award-winning autonomous code and had the opportunity to work closely with mentors who are industry experts (Microsoft, Boeing, etc.). I picked up skills like computer vision, autonomous motion and trajectory planning, PID control, and even Android app development.